Guide to the Pierson College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1951-1973 Maintained by the Master
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Pierson College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1951-1973 maintained by the master
1948-1973
RU 317
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
19.5
The records consist of student records maintained by the master of Pierson College, Yale University.
Pierson College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-J-2 (YRG 13-J-2), Records of the master of Pierson College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the master of Pierson College, Yale University.
Biographical / Historical
The title "Master" for chief executive officers of residential colleges was changed to "Head of College" in April of 2016.
College students; Pierson College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Classes of 1951-1963, 1947-1963; Accession 1972-A-007
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - Student Records
    - Class of 1951 General, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1952 General, 1948-1952 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Class of 1953 General, 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Class of 1954 General, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Class of 1955 General, 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 437)
    - Class of 1956 General, 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 543)
    - Class of 1957 General, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 657)
    - Class of 1958 General, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 756)
    - Class of 1959 General, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 851)
    - Class of 1960 General, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 960)
    - Class of 1961 General, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 1064)
    - Class of 1962 General, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 1152)
    - Class of 1963 General, 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 1236)
- Student records for the Classes of 1964-1973, 1960-1973; Accession 1981-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
  - Class of 1964
  - Class of 1965
  - Class of 1966
  - Class of 1967
  - Class of 1968
  - Class of 1969
  - Class of 1970
  - Class of 1971
  - Class of 1972, 1968-1973 (Box 5–6)
  - Class of 1973